napacabs.com 2016-05-15

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Napacabs.com uses and protects any information that you give Napacabs.com when you use this website. Napacabs.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Napacabs.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at support@napacabs.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 14702 Central Ave Chino, CA 91710.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## List of cookies we collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE name| COOKIE Description  
---|---  
CART| The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO| Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
COMPARE| The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CURRENCY| Your preferred currency  
CUSTOMER| An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH| An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO| An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS| Stores the Customer Segment ID  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE| A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
FRONTEND| You sesssion ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW| Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY| The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT| The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE| Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE| Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART| A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL| The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
POLLN| Information on what polls you have voted on.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED| The items that you have recently compared.  
STF| Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE| The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE| Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS| The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST| An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT| The number of items in your Wishlist.  

NapaCabs.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting NapaCabs.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

##   
**What Personal Information About Customers Does NapaCabs.com Gather?**

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at NapaCabs.com. Here are the types of information we gather.

**Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses NapaCabs.com. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at NapaCabs.com if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist. 

E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from NapaCabs.com if your computer supports such capabilities.

##  **Does NapaCabs.com Share the Information It Receives?**

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only with the subsidiaries NapaCabs.com and NapaCabs, Inc., controls and as described below. 

Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that NapaCabs.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

 **Protection of NapaCabs.com and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of NapaCabs.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

 **With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

##  **What Information Can I Access?**

NapaCabs.com gives you access to the following information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. This list will change as our Web site evolves.

##  **Your Account**

 **Your Wish List  
What Choices Do I Have? **  
As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such NapaCabs.com features as Wish Lists.

You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in the "What Information Can I Access?" section above. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us. (If you do not want to receive Conditions of Use and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of NapaCabs.com, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.)

The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

 **  
Children**  
NapaCabs.com does not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 21, you may use NapaCabs.com only with involvement of a parent or guardian to purchase non-alcohol gifts and accessories.

##   
**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit NapaCabs.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of California. If you have any concern about privacy at NapaCabs.com, please send us a thorough description to Support@NapaCabs.com, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.

##   
**Automatic Information**

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for and phone number used to call our 800 number.

 **  
Send mail to Support with questions or comments about this web site.**
